needhelppayingbills.com 2018-07-31

# Privacy policy

**ADVERTISING**

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a your visits to this website. Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to you  based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated). (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [aboutads](https://www.aboutads.info/)[. ](http://www.aboutads.info.%29/)If you have not opted out of third-party ad serving, the cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads to this site.

**ANALYTICS**

We may collect information about your computer, including your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and in order to create reports. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

The only cookies in use on our site are for Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it. 

Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site.

Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page. 

Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, [visit this Google page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with or advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**WEB BROWSER COOKIES**

Needhelppayingbills.com may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. This is determined by the User's web browser, as they determine this. Not the browser may place cookies on a user's hard drive for record-keeping purposes (to enhance their experience) and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY**

The customer support team or owner of needhelppayingbills.com has the discretion to update all or some of this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to parts of the policy. It can help people stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we or our partners collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS**

By using the information on needhelppayingbills.com, signify your acceptance of these various policies. If you do not agree, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. The policy was updated on 3/19/2017.
